Guide to the Social Service Employees Union Records WAG.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Constitutions and Minutes, 1964-2005
  - Constitution and By-Laws of Welfare Local 371, Nov 23, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Constitution: Proposed, [1968?] (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Constitution, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Constitution, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Constitution, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Constitutional Amendments, 1950s (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Constitutional Amendments, 1960s (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Constitutional Amendments, 1970s (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, Oct 1962-Dec 1964 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Minutes: Executive Board/Committee, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee/Board, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee/Board, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee/Board, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee/Board, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee/Board, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee/Board, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee/Board, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee/Board, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee/Board, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee/Board, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, Jan 2004-May 2004 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, Jun 2004-Dec 2004 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Minutes: General Membership, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Series III: General Files, 1944-2006
  - AFL-CIO: General, 1970s-1990s (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Conference: People, Meeting the Challenge, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - AFSCME Convention, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - AFSCME Officers Manual: Information for Local Union Officers, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - AFSCME Songbook: Carry It On, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - April Actions for Peace, Jobs and Justice: Mobilization in Washington, DC, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Association for Homemaker Services (AHS), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Association of Black Social Workers, 1982-1992 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Association of Supervisors of the Department of Welfare: Membership Application, Undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Bertha Capin Reynolds Society Institute and 3rd Annual Conference: Practicing as a Progressive, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Biographical Information: Caseworkers, 1980s (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Biographical Information: State and Federal Candidates, 1980s (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Black Caucus, Undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Black/Women's Studies, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Block Grant Implementation Manual, Dec 1995 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Building Safety and Health Issues, 1982, 1991-1992, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Bureau of Hospital Care Services (BHCS), 1966 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Button Designs, Undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Calendar for 1985 (20th Anniversary of Strike): Quotations and Related Material, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Calendar for 1990: Quotations and Related Material, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Clendar for 1991: Quotations and Related Material, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Calendar for 1992: Quotations and Related Material, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Case Aides, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Center Newsletters: Bayridge ID, Undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Center Newsletters: Boro Hall Militante and other Boro Hall Newsletters, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Center Newsletters: Brooklyn PSA (Protective Services for Adults) Weekly Reader, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Center Newsletters: Bushwick, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Center Newsletters: Concourse Caucus, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Center Newsletters: Crotona-Tremont Community Action Committee, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Center Newsletters: Dyckman, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Center Newsletters: East End Unionist, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Center Newsletters: Fort Greene Collateral, News, Up Against the Wall, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Center Newsletters: Fulton Forum, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Center Newsletters: Gramercy's The Incredible Bureaucrat, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Center Newsletters: Hamilton's Truthpick, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Center Newsletters: Harlem Untitled, Harlem Voice, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Center Newsletters: Herald Happening, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Center Newsletters: Livingston's The Living Stone, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Center Newsletters: LM [Lower Manhattan] News, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Center Newsletters: Main Street-Shelter Care Center For Men (SCCM), 1985 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Center Newsletters: Melrose, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Center Newsletters: Nevins News, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Center Newsletters: News and Notes of Non Rez [Non-Residential], 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Center Newsletters: Queens, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Center Newsletters: St. Nicholas' The System, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Center Newsletters: Tremont, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Center Newsletters: Williamsburg's What's Happening, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Center Newsletters: Wycoff, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Certification and Pool Lists, Undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Certification and Pool Lists, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Certification and Pool Lists, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Certification and Pool Lists, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Certification and Pool Lists, 1987-1990 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Certification and Pool Lists, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Certification and Pool Lists, 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Certification from Department of Labor, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Chapter: Amsterdam, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Chapter: Bay Ridge, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Chapter: Bergen, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Chapter: Boro Hall, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Chapter: BPA, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Chapter: Brownsville, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Chapter: Bureau of Child Welfare (BCW), 1966-1975 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Chapter: Bushwick, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Chapter: Case Aides, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Chapter: Caseworkers, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Chapter: Chelsea, Undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Chapter: Clerical Local 1549, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Chapter: Clinton, 1965-1971 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Chapter: Crotona, 1969, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Chapter: De Kalb, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Chapter: East End, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Chapter: Euclid, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Chapter: Fort Greene, 1965-1971 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Chapter: Fulton, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Chapter: Gramercy, 1969, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Chapter: Greenwood, 1965, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Chapter: Harlem, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Chapter: Health and Hospital Corporation, 1977, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Chapter: Housing and Development Administration (HAD), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Chapter: Human Resources Administration Employees, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Chapter: Linden, 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Chapter: Livingston, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Chapter: Melrose, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Chapter: Non-Resident (Welfare Center), 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Chapter: Prospect, 1969, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Chapter: Queens, 1963, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Chapter: Richmond, 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Chapter: Shelter and Institutional, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Chapter: Supervisors, 1969-1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Chapter: Veterans, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Chapter: Waverly, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Chapter: Williamsburg, 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Child Care: Newsletters, correspondence, clippings on issues and advocacy, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Child Welfare: Administration for Children's Services (ACS) Services Title Proposals and Related Materials, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Child Welfare: Bureau of Child Welfare (BCW) Replacement Services, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Child Welfare: Child Protective Services - Letters of Notification (Draft), Jul 14, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Child Welfare: Child Protective Services Plan and Day Care Scandal-Press Clippings, Correspondence and Related Materials Regarding Child Abuse Cases, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Child Welfare: Child Welfare Administration: Drafts of Planned Placement Referrals to Foster Care Agencies and Emergency Placement Referrals to Foster Care Agencies, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Child Welfare: Child Welfare Reform Act of 1979, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Child Welfare: "Children Still At Risk: Comments on the Five Year Anniversary of the Administration for Children's Services," a Report by Mark Green and C-PLAN, May 1, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Child Welfare: City of New York Child Welfare Administration: Correspondence, Statistics, Recommendations, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Child Welfare: Closing of Direct Foster Care Services (DFCS) Offices in Manhattan and Staten Island-Press Clippings, Notes and Related Materials, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Child Welfare: Commissioners William Grinker and Barbara Sabol, Press Clippings (includes Testimony before City Council Commission on General Welfare), 1986-1993 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Child Welfare: Connections Computer-Based Training for Foster Care/Placements, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Child Welfare: Death of Elisa Izquierdo, Child Fatality Review Panel and Related Materials, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Child Welfare: Death of Elisa Izquierdo, Legislation and Recommendations, Jan 1996-Mar 1996 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Child Welfare: Death of Elisa Izquierdo, Press Clippings and Related Material, Nov 1995 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Child Welfare: Death of Elisa Izquierdo, Press Clippings and Related Material, Dec 1995 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Child Welfare: Death of Elisa Izquierdo, Press Clippings and Related Material (includes report of the Vacco Commission), Apr 1996 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Child Welfare: Death of Elisa Izquierdo and Other Related Cases and Events, May 1996-Nov 1996 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Child Welfare: Death of Nixzmary Brown, Media Overview Prepared for District Council 37 Executive Board, Jan 12, 2006-Feb 8, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Child Welfare: Death of Nixzmary Brown, Press Clippings and Related Materials, Jan 12, 2006-Jan 16, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Child Welfare: Death of Nixzmary Brown, Press Clippings and Related Materials, Jan 17, 2006-Jan 31, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Child Welfare: Death of Nixzmary Brown, Press Clippings and Related Materials and Press Clippings re: Administration for Children's Services (ACS), Jan 2006-May 2006 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Child Welfare: General Reports and Comments, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Child Welfare: Group Facilities-Correspondence, Press Clippings and Related Materials, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Child Welfare: Local 371 Demonstrations, 1984, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Child Welfare: Mayor's Management Advisory Task Force/ Dinkins' Foster Care Commission, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Child Welfare: Mayor's (HRA) Management Report, Sep 1988 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Child Welfare: New York City Child Welfare Advisory Panel, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Child Welfare: Placement Crisis Press Clippings and Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Child Welfare: Press Clippings, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Child Welfare: Press Clippings, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Child Welfare: Press Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Child Welfare: Press Clippings, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Child Welfare: Press Clippings, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Child Welfare: Press Clippings, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Child Welfare: Press Clippings, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Child Welfare: Press Clippings, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Child Welfare: Press Clippings, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Child Welfare: Press Clippings, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Child Welfare: Press Clippings and Related Materials, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Child Welfare: Press Clippings and Related Materials, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Child Welfare: Press Clippings, Undated, 1999-2001 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Child Welfare: Problems in Emergency Children's Services (ECS), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Child Welfare: Protocol for Handling Emergency Abuse/Neglect Cases Draft Memorandum, [1994?] (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Child Welfare: Reorganization of Protective Services in Special Services for Children (SSC), Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Child Welfare: Review of Investigations, Assessments and Decision Making in Child Abuse and Maltreatment Reports Received by the Child Welfare Administration of New York City, Apr 1996 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Child Welfare: Special Services for Children (SSC)-Child Protection Act of 1973 and Related Materials, 1976-1981 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Child Welfare: SSC Reforms-Press Release, Correspondence and Related Material, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Child Welfare: "Special Services for Children: Profiles in Failure" by Linda Schleicher in Catalyst, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Child Welfare: Washington Hearings on Child Welfare System Crisis-Press Clippings, Correspondence and Related Materials (includes testimony of Suella Gallup), Apr 1988 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Child Welfare: "Working for the Rights of Children" Conference, Oct 13, 1989-Oct 14, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - City of New York Office of Communications, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - City of New York Office of Labor Relations, 1967-1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - City of New York Office of Municipal Labor Relations, 1981-1986 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - City of New York Office of the Mayor: Executive Orders, 1973, 1978, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Citywide Coordinating Committee of Welfare Groups, 1967-1971 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Civil Rights Act of 1990 and Related Materials, 1990s (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Classification Appeals and Salary Differential for Graduate Study, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Clean Sweep: An Office of Community Education (OCE) News Coverage Os Special Services for Children (SSC) Concerns, 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Clerical-Administrative Coloring Book for City Employees, Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Coalition for a Nuclear-Free Harbor and Related Issues and Organizations, 1984-1990 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Commissioner's Report to the Staff, Apr 1967-Jul 1967, Oct 1967 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Committee: Ad Hoc Committee (Field), 1968 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Committee: Advisory Committee to the Contractual Committees, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Committee: Affiliations, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Committee: Civil Rights, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Committee: Civil Service, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Committee: Client Advisory (East End Welfare Center), 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Committee: Community Action, Undated, 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Committee: Community Relations and Services, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Committee: Concerned Social Workers/Correspondence, 1981-1991 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Committee: Concerned Social Workers/Mailing Lists and Raffle Ticket Sales, Undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Committee: Concerned Social Workers/Minutes, Membership Lists, Scholarship Fund and Related Materials, 1981-1987 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Committee: Concerned Social Workers Newsletter, 1982-1991 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Committee: Constitutional, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Committee: Dance, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Committee: Downtown Brooklyn Organizing, 1960s (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Committee: Dues, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Committee: Education and Research, 1960s (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Committee: Election, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Committee: Election, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Committee: Election, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Committee: Executive, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Committee: Finance, 1965, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Committee: Finance, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Committee: Finance, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Committee: Finance, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Committee: Human Rights, 1960s (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Committee: Labor-Management, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Committee: Labor-Management, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Committee: Labor-Management, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Committee: Labor-Management, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Committee: Labor-Management, 1969, 1970-1973, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Committee: Legal Assistance, 1972-1975 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Committee: Legal Assistance, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Committee: Legal Assistance, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Committee: Legislative and Political Action, 1969-1974 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Committee: Legislative and Political Action, May 1976-Dec 1976 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Committee: Legislative and Political Action, Jan 1977-Mar 1977 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Committee: Legislative and Political Action, Apr 1977-Jul 1977 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Committee: Legislative and Political Action, Aug 1977-Dec 1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Committee: Legislative and Political Action, 1985-1990, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Committee: Negotiating, 1968, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Committee: Nominating, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Committee: Personnel, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Committee: Plant Management, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Committee: Professional Standards, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Committee: Program and Policy, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Committee: Rank and File, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Committee: Recall, Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Committee: Reorganization and Workload, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Committee: Service, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Committee: Social Service-Overwork, Undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Committee: Trustees Election, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Committee: Women's, 1980s, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Committee: Work Action, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Committee: Workload/Issues and Reports, 1958-1983 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Committee for Effective Leadership, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Political Education (COPE), Undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Community Alternative Systems Agency (CASA): Fight to Save CASA, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Community Development Agency, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Condon-Wadlin Law and Taylor Law, 1966, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Conference: New Staff Program at George Meany Center, Jun 4, 1989-Jun 16, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Conference: SSEU Local 371, Oct 25, 1987-Oct 27, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Conference: Women Fighting Poverty Conference VIII "Women Together-A Force For Change, Mar 24, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Conference: Work, Welfare, Reform: Redefining the Debate, Sep 28, 1987-Sep 29, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Conference on Welfare Reform: Presented by the Advisory Board of the New York City Human Resources Administration, May 29, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Conferences and Related Events: General, 1974-1993 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Contributions and Support, 1960s-1990s (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: AFSCME (includes Report for year ended Feb 28, 1966), 1960-1996 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: Assaults on Field Workers, 1965-1970 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence: Babcock, Gamble Trust Fund, 1969-1976 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence: Banking, 1965-1974 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence: Basilio, Anthony (Secretary-Treasurer), 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence: Benson, John (Chairman of Organization then Vice-President), 1966-1970 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence: Blumenson, Neil (Education Director), 1970-1972 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence: Brown, John (Acting Administrator), 1992 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence: Buccinna, Nicholas (Vice-President then President), 1960-1965 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence: Cacchione, Bernard (1st Vice-President), 1966 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence: Caldwell, Patricia (Vice-President), 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence: Charap, Fred (Administrator), 1975-1977 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence: Cohen, Bart (Vice-President then President), 1966-1974 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence: Coulthurst, Milton (Vice-President), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 43)